careerdubai.com 2015-10-22

# CareerDubai.net Dubai, Jobs in Dubai, career in Dubai, DUBAI JOBS, JOBS IN UAE

**Overview**

Careerdubai.net ("Careerdubai.net") is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the Careerdubai.net Web site. By creating an account on the Careerdubai.net Web site, you consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement. 

**Collection and Retention of Information**

In order to provide you the services of Careerdubai.net, in some areas of our Web sites, Careerdubai.net requests or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In order to continually enhance your use of Careerdubai.net and to provide you requested information about Careerdubai.net third party partners, in other areas, Careerdubai.net may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your postal code, preferences, interests and favorites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. 

We also gather or may gather certain information about your use of our site, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by Careerdubai.net. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used to evaluate different aspects of the Careerdubai.net Web Site. The information may also be used for site security and law enforcement purposes. 

Careerdubai.net may sometimes afford you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioural, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services. 

**Use of Information by Careerdubai.net**

We use the information we gather on the Careerdubai.net Web site, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the Careerdubai.net Web site, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the Careerdubai.net site, such as new Careerdubai.net opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you 

**Disclosure of Information to Others**

We do not disclose to third parties your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of the Careerdubai.net Web site (such as the areas you visit or the services you access), except as set forth in the following four subparagraphs. 

1\. We may disclose such information to third parties if you consent to such disclosure. For example, if you indicate that you would like to receive information about the products or services of third parties at the time you register for a My Careerdubai.net account, we may supply your contact information to third parties such as employers, recruiters, data aggregators, marketers or others for the purpose of sending you e-mail or otherwise communicating with you. We may use data we have about you (such as the interests and preferences you have expressed) to determine whether you might be interested in the products or services of a particular third-party. 

2\. We may disclose such information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 

3\. We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Careerdubai.net or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 

4\. We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of Careerdubai.net's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event Careerdubai.net becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, Careerdubai.net or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. 

Careerdubai.net may also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to its Web site with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors that visit Careerdubai.net's site and how those visitors use the site. 

**Updating Your Information**

You have the right to demand that your personal information be deleted from Careerdubai.net. You may review, correct, update or change your My Careerdubai.net account profile information at any time by simply logging into your My Careerdubai.net account, going to your Account Profile, and editing it with the options provided. You may review, delete, correct, update or change your résumé on Careerdubai.net at any time by simply logging into your My Careerdubai.net account, going to Manage résumés, and deleting it or editing it with the options provided. You can request that your My Careerdubai.net account be deleted by contacting Careerdubai.net. 

**Security**

Careerdubai.net has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

**Changes to Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our Privacy Statement for Careerdubai.net, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.
